<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<documentation>
  <section title="">
    <![CDATA[
      <div>
        This document is a guideline to use the AviaryFX PHP SDK.
      </div>
      <h3>Step 0: Instantiate an AviaryFX object</h3>
      <div>
        The first step is to instantiate an AviaryFX object:
        <pre class='code'>

$aviaryfx = new AviaryFX($api_key, $api_secret);
        </pre>
        Once an instance of the class has been instantiated, you can call the methods like: <em>aviaryfx->getFilters()</em>, etc
      </div>
      <h3>Step 1: Get a list of filters</h3>
      <div>
        To retrieve a list of filters that can be used to render images call the <em>aviaryfx->getFilters()</em> method. 
        This returns an array of filters with label, uid, thumb, description and parameter list for each filter.
      </div>
      <h3>Step 2: Upload an image to the AviaryFX server</h3>
      <div>
       To upload an image file to the AviaryFX server use the <em>aviaryfx->upload()</em> method. This method returns
       an array with a url to the file on the server. The returned url should be used for subsequent interactions.
      </div>
      <h3>Step 3: Render thumbnails</h3>
      <div>
        Once a filter is selected call <em>aviaryfx->renderOptions()</em> to render a thumbnail grid. 
        This returns an array with a url to the thumbnail grid and render option parameters for each of the requested number of options for that filter.
      </div>
      <h3>Step 4: Render full image</h3>
      <div>
        Once an option is selected call <em>aviaryfx->render()</em> along with the filter ID, image url and the parameters for the selected option.
        This returns an array with the URL to rendered image.
      </div>
    ]]>
  </section>
  <section title="Quickstart Code">
    <![CDATA[
        <div class="">
            The following code sample will instantiate an AviaryFX object:
        </div>
        <div class="">
            <div class="code">
                <pre>
                
require_once("AviaryFX.php");

$api_key = "demoapp";
$api_secret = "demoappsecret";
	
$aviaryfx = new AviaryFX($api_key, $api_secret);
                </pre>
            </div>
        </div>
    ]]>
  </section>
</documentation>